Boss
رئيس
inside
داخل
Xie
شي
Didn't expect it; I didn't come looking for you
لم أتوقع ذلك؛ لم آتِ أبحث عنك
yet you came knocking yourself
لكنك أتيتَ تُسمّي نفسك
Boss Cheng wouldn't, about the past,
رفض الرئيس تشنغ الحديث عن الماضي.
still hold a grudge, right?
ما زلت تحمل ضغينة، أليس كذلك؟
If it weren't for you
لولاك
I wouldn't have stayed abroad that long
ما كنت لأبقى في الخارج كل هذه المدة
A Shan (Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org)
أ شان (مسؤول الدعم، شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org)
Cut off his hand for me
اقطع يده من أجلي
Don't move
لا تتحرك
Wait
انتظر
Don't you want to hear why I came today?
ألا تريد أن تسمع لماذا جئت اليوم؟
Back then, in Haicheng,
في ذلك الوقت، في هايتشنغ،
you were quite a big name
لقد كنت اسماً كبيراً جداً
you got the wind when you asked,
لقد حصلت على الريح عندما سألت،
and the rain when you asked
والمطر عندما سألت
Now you're content just guarding a warehouse here?
هل أنت راضٍ الآن بمجرد حراسة مستودع هنا؟
Your woman was snatched
لقد تم اختطاف حبيبتك
You're willing to let it slide like that?
هل أنت مستعد للتغاضي عن الأمر بهذه الطريقة؟
What Zheng Nanfeng is holding in his arms now
ما يحمله تشنغ نانفنغ بين ذراعيه الآن
is your wife
هل زوجتك
the seat he's sitting on
المقعد الذي يجلس عليه
was supposed to be yours
كان من المفترض أن يكون لك
Now he's taken everything
لقد أخذ كل شيء الآن
Are you willing to accept that?
هل أنت مستعد لقبول ذلك؟
What on earth are you trying to say?
ما الذي تحاول قوله بالضبط؟
Don't be snide with me
لا تكن ساخرًا معي
We're on the same boat now
نحن الآن في نفس المركب
We have a common goal
لدينا هدف مشترك
It's Zheng Nanfeng
إنه تشنغ نانفنغ
Boss Xie, do you know
يا رئيس شي، هل تعلم
I'm currently working with Zheng Nanfeng
أعمل حاليًا مع تشنغ نانفنغ
That's bullshit cooperation
هذا تعاون زائف
Just an errand-boy gig
مجرد وظيفة ساعي بريد
Say that again
قل ذلك مرة أخرى
Easy, Boss Cheng
سهل يا رئيس تشنغ
I said we're on the same boat
قلت إننا في نفس المركب
I can take back everything you lost
أستطيع أن أستعيد كل ما فقدته
all of it
كل ذلك
You alone?
هل أنت وحدك؟
Don't get yourself tossed back inside
لا تدع نفسك تُلقى في الداخل مرة أخرى
On my own is not enough
بمفردي لا يكفي
But I wonder
لكنني أتساءل
Is Master Hong enough?
هل يكفي السيد هونغ؟
You know Master Hong?
هل تعرف السيد هونغ؟
Oh
أوه
I was inside with him
كنت بالداخل معه
But now his network is in my hands
لكن شبكته الآن في يدي
If you join forces with me
إذا انضممت إليّ
taking on Zheng Nanfeng won't be a problem
مواجهة تشنغ نانفنغ لن تشكل مشكلة
So what's your plan now?
إذن ما هي خطتك الآن؟
No
لا
Absolutely not
لا على الإطلاق
What?
ماذا؟
Scared?
مقدس؟
I, Cheng Yadong,
أنا، تشنغ يادونغ،
have hustled for years,
لقد كافحوا لسنوات،
what have I ever feared?
ما الذي كنت أخشاه يوماً؟
No reason to refuse me
لا يوجد سبب لرفضي
I have my own way of doing things
لدي طريقتي الخاصة في فعل الأشياء
I know Boss Cheng is someone
أعرف أن الرئيس تشنغ شخص ما
who won't settle for second place
من لا يرضى بالمركز الثاني
I hope you'll think it over
أتمنى أن تفكر في الأمر
I don't need to think it over
لا أحتاج إلى التفكير في الأمر
Thanks
شكرًا
Please
لو سمحت
So absolute, huh?
مطلق للغاية، أليس كذلك؟
I'm afraid I might change my mind
أخشى أن أغير رأيي
Boss Xie won't even get out this door
لن يخرج الرئيس شي من هذا الباب
Fine
بخير
We'll meet again
سنلتقي مجدداً
Boss
رئيس
It seems this Cheng Yadong
يبدو أن هذا تشنغ يادونغ
really doesn't want to work with us
لا يرغب حقاً في العمل معنا
At some moment
في لحظة ما
he was already tempted
لقد كان بالفعل مُغرى
It's just that people like him
الأمر ببساطة أن الناس يحبونه
are a bit hesitant
مترددون بعض الشيء
Looks like we need to add fuel to the fire
يبدو أننا بحاجة إلى صب الزيت على النار
and heat him up from behind
وأشعله من الخلف
I don't think he's that capable
لا أعتقد أنه يتمتع بتلك القدرات
to deal with Zheng Nanfeng
للتعامل مع تشنغ نانفنغ
We can do it without him just the same
يمكننا القيام بذلك بدونه بنفس القدر
Zheng Nanfeng is on the rise now
يشهد تشنغ نانفنغ صعوداً ملحوظاً الآن
with Deep Harbor Group backing him
بدعم من مجموعة ديب هاربور
To take down someone like that
إسقاط شخص كهذا
we must win over
يجب أن نكسب تأييد
people we can use
أشخاص يمكننا الاستعانة بهم
Then this fire
ثم هذه النار
how do we plan to burn it?
كيف نخطط لحرقها؟
Doesn't he make milk powder?
ألا يصنع مسحوق الحليب؟
We'll work that angle
سنعمل على هذا الجانب
Got it
فهمتها
For anyone who won't get on board
لكل من لا يرغب في الانضمام
we'll tie him onto the boat
سنربطه بالقارب
Nanfeng
نانفينج
This is the order Youyou transferred from the mall
هذا هو الطلب الذي قمت بتحويله من المركز التجاري
What?
ماذا؟
It's infant formula again
إنها حليب الأطفال مرة أخرى
A well-known overseas brand
علامة تجارية عالمية معروفة
I heard it's a nationally distributed product
سمعت أنه منتج يتم توزيعه على مستوى البلاد
The distribution volume is high
حجم التوزيع مرتفع
So demand is high
لذا فإن الطلب مرتفع
The merchant wants our logistics channel to speed shipping
يرغب التاجر في أن تعمل قنواتنا اللوجستية على تسريع عملية الشحن
No problem
لا مشكلة
I'll have A Ming and A Qiang handle it personally
سأوكل الأمر إلى آ مينغ وآ تشيانغ شخصياً
Okay
تمام
Remember to drink water
تذكر أن تشرب الماء
Why did you two come in person?
لماذا حضرتما شخصياً؟
Brother Nanfeng told us to
أخبرنا الأخ نانفنغ بـ
Get to work
ابدأ العمل
Fine
بخير
Do a good job
قم بعمل جيد
Stay sharp in a bit
ابقَ متيقظًا بعد قليل
Stick to the plan
التزم بالخطة
Okay
تمام
Go ahead
تفضل
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
You seem a bit distracted today
يبدو أنك مشتت الذهن قليلاً اليوم
It's nothing, it's nothing
لا شيء، لا شيء
We can't be careless about things at the dock
لا يمكننا التهاون بشأن الأمور في الميناء
If anything comes up, remember to tell me
إذا طرأ أي شيء، فتذكر أن تخبرني.
Understood
مفهوم
Is the handover done?
هل تم تسليم المشروع؟
It's all taken care of
تم الاهتمام بكل شيء
Then get back to work
ثم عد إلى العمل
I'll talk with A Qiang alone for a bit
سأتحدث مع آ تشيانغ على انفراد لبعض الوقت
Okay
تمام
Still mad at me?
هل ما زلت غاضباً مني؟
It's all in the past
كل ذلك أصبح من الماضي
Let's go
دعنا نذهب
Don't be mad
لا تغضب
I'll arrange drinks tonight
سأرتب المشروبات الليلة
A Qiang
آ تشيانغ
Put it away properly
ضعه في مكانه بشكل صحيح
Bring that over here
أحضر ذلك إلى هنا
All loaded up, right?
تم تحميل كل شيء، أليس كذلك؟
Loaded up
محملة
Get in the truck
اصعد إلى الشاحنة
Brother Nanfeng
الأخ نانفنغ
Something's wrong
هناك خطب ما
We have a big problem
لدينا مشكلة كبيرة
Some babies who drank our formula
بعض الأطفال الذين شربوا حليبنا الصناعي
are all poisoned
جميعهم مسمومون
They're in emergency treatment at the hospital now
يخضعون الآن للعلاج الطارئ في المستشفى
It's infant formula—how could it go wrong?
إنه حليب أطفال - كيف يمكن أن تسوء الأمور؟
Isn't it a genuine big-brand product?
أليس هذا منتجاً أصلياً من علامة تجارية كبيرة؟
Could there be some misunderstanding?
هل يمكن أن يكون هناك سوء فهم؟
Or some slip-up occurred
أو حدث خطأ ما
I went to verify the batch number of the goods
ذهبت للتحقق من رقم دفعة البضائع
I even checked the can code
حتى أنني تحققت من رمز العلبة
It was indeed the batch we transported
كانت بالفعل هي الدفعة التي نقلناها.
Are you sure you
هل أنت متأكد؟
checked the can code for that batch
تم التحقق من رمز العلبة لتلك الدفعة
is this batch
هل هذه الدفعة
I didn't look into that in detail
لم أبحث في ذلك بالتفصيل
But it's definitely that batch
لكنها بالتأكيد تلك الدفعة
There's definitely a problem here
هناك مشكلة بالتأكيد هنا
A Ming
أ مينغ
Pass the word down
انقل الخبر
Pull this problematic batch from shelves
اسحب هذه الدفعة المعيبة من الرفوف
Okay
تمام
A Qiang
آ تشيانغ
Whatever it takes,
مهما تطلب الأمر،
get me the cans of the formula involved
أحضر لي علب التركيبة المستخدمة
Check again
تحقق مرة أخرى
Okay
تمام
Zhiyi
تشيي
Please make a trip to the formula factory
يرجى القيام برحلة إلى مصنع التركيبات
Bring their quality inspection director
أحضروا مدير مراقبة الجودة الخاص بهم
and the outbound supervisor to come over
ومشرف الرحلات الخارجية ليأتي
I need to investigate this from the start
أحتاج إلى التحقيق في هذا الأمر من البداية
Okay
تمام
I'll contact them now
سأتصل بهم الآن
Don't panic
لا تُصب بالذعر
Okay
تمام
Great
عظيم
Brother
أخ
The public outcry is huge right now
الغضب الشعبي هائل الآن
And many families
والعديد من العائلات
have started coming out to demand answers
بدأوا بالخروج للمطالبة بإجابات
Not enough
غير كافٍ
Far from enough
غير كافٍ على الإطلاق
Here is the plan
إليكم الخطة
Go to the TV station
اذهب إلى محطة التلفزيون
Find Reporter Jiang
ابحث عن المراسل جيانغ
He is my friend
هو صديقي
Have him back you up
اجعله يدعمك
I want all Haicheng news media
أريد من جميع وسائل الإعلام الإخبارية في هايتشنغ
to report this
للإبلاغ عن هذا
Once it gets big enough,
بمجرد أن يكبر بما فيه الكفاية،
he, Zheng Nanfeng,
هو، تشنغ نانفنغ،
even with three heads and six arms, will not escape
حتى بثلاثة رؤوس وستة أذرع، لن يفلت
Okay, I'll go now
حسناً، سأذهب الآن
Wait
انتظر
Then go arrange some people
ثم اذهب ورتب أمور بعض الأشخاص
Find those moms
ابحث عن هؤلاء الأمهات
Have them call the Bureau of Market Regulation
اطلب منهم الاتصال بمكتب تنظيم السوق
and the Administration for Industry and Commerce to complain
ولإدارة الصناعة والتجارة تقديم شكوى
and write complaint letters
وكتابة رسائل الشكوى
Okay
تمام
Brother Nanfeng
الأخ نانفنغ
People from the Administration for Industry and Commerce are here
يتواجد هنا موظفون من إدارة الصناعة والتجارة
You are Mr. Zheng Nanfeng, right?
أنت السيد تشنغ نانفينغ، أليس كذلك؟
That is me
هذا أنا
We are with the Administration for Industry and Commerce
نحن تابعون لإدارة الصناعة والتجارة
We received a complaint
تلقينا شكوى
There is a batch of tainted milk powder
هناك دفعة من مسحوق الحليب الملوث
was transported in through your company's dock
تم نقلها عبر رصيف شركتكم
We will now, by law, investigate and sanction your company
سنقوم الآن، بموجب القانون، بالتحقيق مع شركتكم ومعاقبتها.
and ask you to cooperate with our next steps
ونرجو منكم التعاون معنا في خطواتنا التالية
Okay
تمام
I miss you
أفتقدك
Whenever dusk comes
كلما حل الغسق
the evening wind blows
تهب رياح المساء
I miss you
أفتقدك
The riddle of life
لغز الحياة
Try not to see it clearly
حاول ألا تراه بوضوح
Close your eyes
أغمض عينيك
Do not respond
لا ترد
The evening wind blows and blows
تهب رياح المساء وتهب بقوة.
Go with the wind
انطلق مع الريح
Tonight, children, do not cry in secret
الليلة يا أطفال، لا تبكوا سراً
Do not cry in secret
لا تبكِ في السر
The evening wind blows and blows
تهب رياح المساء وتهب بقوة.
Go with the wind
انطلق مع الريح
With nightfall and stars,
مع حلول الليل وظهور النجوم،
drift gently to sleep
استسلم للنوم بهدوء
Let the evening wind blow
دع نسيم المساء يهب